gozefo.com 2015-09-19

# Zefo | Used Furniture. Zero Effort.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Our Privacy Policy explains: 

  1. What information we collect. 
  2. How we collect and use that information. 
  3. How should you provide information selectively, and how to access and update information. 
  4. Information sharing and protection, and the application and changes of this Privacy Policy. 

**Information we collect**

We collect information from you _inter alia_ for the following purposes (i) providing you with our services; (ii) improving our services; (iii) improving our business as a whole; (iv) analysing data, tracking trends, creating databases for rating systems, recommendation engines, bidding algorithms etc.; (v) research; (vi) legal requirements and (vii) transfer of such information, by way of sale or otherwise etc. (collectively referred to as the “ **Purposes** ”). 

We will collect two types of information from you. 

Personal Information (as described below) and Non-personal Information (all other information). 

If we combine Personal Information with Non-personal Information technically, as long as they stay combined, such information will be deemed as Personal Information. 

For the purposes of this Policy ‘Personal Information’ means any information relating to an individual which directly or indirectly, in combination with other information available or likely to be available with Zefo (“ **Us** ” or “ **We** ”), is capable of indentifying the individual and includes, without limitation name, gender, city and other information such as profession, photos uploaded and profile information. 

We do not, however, collect ‘Sensitive Personal Data or Information’ which consists of information relating to: 

  1. Password other than the password used for accessing the Website; 
  2. Sexual orientation; 
  3. Medical records and history; and 
  4. Biometric information. 

**YOU ARE HEREBY ADVISED TO REFRAIN FROM PROVIDING TO US OR UPLOADING ON THE WEBSITE ANY SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION. IN THE EVENT YOU PROVIDE OR UPLOAD ANY SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE, EITHER INADVERTANTLY OR OTHERWISE, YOU HEREBY ABSOLVE US FROM ANY AND ALL LIABILITY IN RELATION TO THE COLLECTION, RETENTION, TRANSFER AND STORAGE OF SUCH SENSITIVE PERSONAL DATA OR INFORMATION.**

**How we collect and use information**

Information we get from your use of our services 

When you interact with Zefo, you may be asked to provide your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information in order to use our services. We may use and combine Personal Information we collect from all of our services with Non-Personal Information to provide, maintain, protect and improve our services. You hereby agree that Zefo may collect, use and/or disclose the Personal Information for the Purposes as set out in this policy. 

The following are types of information which we may collect and examples how we use such information. Please note that the information described below and how it is used are examples, and are not exhaustive. 

The collection of Information 

  * When you create an account on the Website, we’ll ask for certain information, including but not limited to your name, telephone number, e-mail address and delivery address. 
  * When you use our services other users can see the Personal Information that you share. You bear the sole legal responsibility for all Personal Information uploaded / shared by you. 
  * When you use location-based applications and features, we will collect your location information. 
  * We use cookies and various technologies to collect and store Personal and Non-personal Information when you use our Website. 
  * When you visit the Website, we will automatically collect and store information in server logs. Such server log information may include: IP address, browser type, browser language, referral URL, operating system, and date and time stamp and click-stream data. 

The use of Information 

  * Zefo will strictly follow this Privacy Policy as well as the updates hereof when using your Personal Information. Your Personal Information will only be used for the Purposes. For any other uses, we will ask you for permission. 
  * The Personal Information may be used to make our Website better, however, in most cases we will only use comprehensive information and statistical information for such purpose. 
  * The Personal Information may be used to communicate with you, to deliver customized content to you, to analyse data, track trends, create databases for rating systems, recommendation engines, bidding algorithms and transfer such information. 
  * We may also use your information to improve our services and analyze the efficiency of our business operation. 
  * We use cookies and various technologies (such as pixel tags) to collect information to improve our services and overall service quality. We use pixel tags to send email messages in a format our users can read, and they tell us whether they have read. We may use this information to reduce or eliminate messages sent to users. 
  * While not all cookies collect personal data, some can potentially collect personal data. When you enable the use of cookies for your internet activities, you are deemed to have consented to the use of cookies to collect, use, and disclose personal data you provide. You can configure your web browser to suit your cookie preferences, i.e. to accept or reject certain categories of cookies, or choose to receive a notification if there are cookies about to be created. 

[Accessing and updating your Personal Information 

Click on [www.Zefo.com](https://gozefo.com/) to log in to your account, you are able to access and update your Personal Information. You can delete part of Personal Information or request us to delete your personal account, which we would do, unless we must keep certain information for legal purposes. 

We aim to maintain our services in a manner that protects information from accidental or malicious destruction. Because of this, after you delete information from our services, we may not immediately delete residual copies from our active servers and may not remove information from our backup systems. ] 

Information we share with third parties 

We will ensure the confidentiality of your Personal Information. You are authorizing us to share your Personal Information with a third party without the requirement of any further consent in the following cases: 

  * Cases in which disclosure as required or authorised based on the applicable laws and/or regulations or as required by a court or tribunal or other law enforcement agency. 
  * Cases in which the purpose of such disclosure is clearly in your interests, and if consent cannot be obtained in a timely way. 
  * Cases in which the disclosure is necessary to respond to an emergency that threatens the life, health or safety of yourself or another individual. 
  * Cases in which disclosure is necessary for any investigation or proceedings. 
  * Cases in which the disclosure is to a public agency and such disclosure is necessary in the public interest. 
  * Where such disclosure without your consent is permitted by law. 

Such third parties may include: 

  * our associated or affiliated organisations or related entities; 
  * any of our agents, contractors or third party service providers that process or will be processing your personal data on our behalf including but not limited to those which provide administrative or other services to us such as mailing houses, telecommunication companies, information technology companies and data centres; and 
  * third parties to whom disclosure by Zefo is for one or more of the Purposes. 

Subject to applicable law, Zefo may, at its sole discretion, transfer Personal Information to any other body corporate (as defined under the Information Technology Act, 2000) that ensures at least the same level of data protection as is provided by Zefo under the terms hereof, whether located in India or any other country. By using the Website, you accept the terms hereof and you hereby consent to the storage and processing of information in any of the above locations. By continuing to use the Website, you provide your consent for transfer, sharing and disclosure of such Personal Information by Zefo in accordance with this Privacy Policy 

**Information security**

Zefo endeavors to maintain physical, technical and procedural safeguards that are appropriate to protect your Personal Information against loss, misuse, copying, damage or modification and unauthorized access or disclosure. 

**When this Privacy Policy applies**

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to Services offered by third parties including other users on our Website. We strongly suggest that you directly agree upon a suitable privacy policy or confidentiality terms with such third parties or users before you share information with them. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to other sites linked from the Website. 

**Changes**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy, at any time without providing you any prior written notice. By continuing to access or use the Website after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. 

Further information 

If you have any questions, complaints or concerns about Zefo’s Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us by sending an email to [help@Zefo.com.] 

Governing Law, Jurisdiction and Dispute resolution 

These terms of this Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of India without regard to its conflict of laws provisions and the parties agrees to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the competent courts in Bengaluru, India to resolve any legal matter arising from the Privacy Policy. In the event a dispute arises between you and Zefo, please contact Zefo. 

Grievance Officer 

In accordance with The Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below: 

You may write to Karan at the following e-mail address 

Karan@gozefo.com
